

DANIEL ADRIAN

Software Enginee



Jln. Gardenia I AA1 No. 1, Bekasi Selatan, 17147 •

+62 8788 512 9698



stefanus daniel adrian @outlook.com Q

www.danieladrian.net

ABOUT ME

I graduated in Electrical Engineering major with a focus on Computer Systems at Trisakti University with GPA 3.59 Cum Laude. 2 years of experience in hardware, microcontroller and robotics, 5 years of experience in Web Development and 2 years of experience in Mobile Application Development. Most of the time, I use PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS and MySQL to develop web application. Moreover, I have tried different programming language like R and Phyton to develop specific solution for analytics and statistic purposes. For mobile application, I have experience in Android and IOS environment. I have an Associate Android Developer certificate from Google Developers. Right now, I handle all Android application in PT. Nova Teknologi Awani. With my strength in software and hardware, I am confidence, I can create better solution for world's problem.

FDUCATION

Formal Education

2011 - 2015

Trisakti University

Electrical Engineering with concentration in Computer System GPA: Cum Laude (3.59 / 4.00)

2008 - 2011

SMAK 7 Penabur

Natural Science

Informal Education

2017

Associate Android Developer

Google Developers http://bit.ly/20y93Hk

2017

Machine Learning

Stanford University on Coursera http://bit.ly/20vj486

2016

ARM and RTOS

Microcontroller Training Next System Bandung

2012

Application and programming of AVR microcontroller

WORLD ROBOTIC EXPLORER

ORGANIZATION

O 2014

Himpunan Mahasiswa Elektro

Trisakti

Research and Development

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2017 - Present

Mobile Application Developer

PT. Nova Teknologi Awani Create and improve all Hellobill Android application.

🔷 Oct 2015 - Jan 2016

Freelance Programmer

PT. Aslamindo Mitra Lestari Create simonev application for ESDM in Research and Development Department

5 2012 - 2016

Freelance Programmer

Trisakti University

0 2015

Teacher

SMAK 7 Penabur

Teaching Pascal Language and animation

ACHIEVEMENT & REWARD

Q 2015

Special Award

International Joint Conference Indonesia Malaysia Bangladesh and Ireland IJCIMBI 2015 Daffodil University

2010

2nd Winner Web Design Competition

UPH University

CONFERENCE & SEMINAR

Speaker

0 2015

International Joint Conference IJCIMBI 2015

Ubudiyah University, Banda Aceh

Participant

Q 2014

Totally Integrated Automation

ITB & Siemens

2013

Digital Broadcasting Technology

Trisakti University

PERSONAL PROJECT

PHP Framework

I created my own PHP
Framework with MVC structure.

Line Follower Project
Trisakti University

Chess Robot Project
Trisakti University

Worm Virus Project

This is the beginning of my journey in computer programming.

LANGUAGE & SKILL

Language Indonesia (Native)

English

Certificate: TOEFL IBT

Score: 90

Programming PHP, MySQL, HTML,

Language Javascript, CSS, Jquery, C,

Go Lang, VB.Net, Java, Kotlin, Swift, Pascal, Assembly, G-code, Phyton

Music Piano, Keyboard,

Intrument Saxophone, Violin, Angklung

daniel.adrian12

in

http://bit.ly/2YzpmZ8

†

http://bit.ly/2JU8kl8 http://bit.ly/2CLhAlD